<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Valorant Application</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="registration_screen">Registration Screen</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="other">Other</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="information">Information</string>

    <string name="return_text">Can\'t be empty!</string>
    <string name="return_conpass_text">Password Not matching!</string>
    <string name="return_email_text">Invalid Email Address!</string>
    <string name="field_toast">Field is required!</string>

    <string name="image_text">image/*</string>

    //Alert Dialog
    <string name="text_alert_dialog">Are you sure!</string>
    <string name="question_alert_dialog">Do you want to close the app?</string>
    <string name="yes_alert_dialog">Yes</string>
    <string name="no_alert_dialog">No</string>

    //Quiz
    <string name="info">Info</string>
    <string name="quiz">Quiz</string>
    <string name="start_game">Start Game</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="please_enter_your_name">Please enter your name</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>

    <string name="agents">Agents</string>
    <string name="maps">Maps</string>
    <string name="weapons">Weapons</string>

    <string name="answer">Answer...</string>
    <string name="send_answer">Send Answer</string>

    //Agents
    <string name="first_question_agents">First Question</string>
    <string name="explanation_of_quest_1_agents">You can hear only one time the voice line of the agent. Your question is:</string>
    <string name="question_one_agents">Who is this Agent?</string>

    <string name="second_question_agents">Second Question</string>
    <string name="explanation_of_quest_2_agents">You have part of the picture of some agent. Your question is:</string>
    <string name="question_second_agents">Who is this Agent?</string>
    <string name="sova">Sova</string>
    <string name="brimstone">Brimstone</string>
    <string name="harbor">Harbor</string>
    <string name="chamber">Chamber</string>

    <string name="third_question_agents">Third Question</string>
    <string name="explanation_of_quest_3_agents">You have video with a sound of ult on someone agent. Your question is:</string>
    <string name="question_third_agents">Who is this Agent?</string>

    <string name="fourth_question_agents">Fourth Question</string>
    <string name="explanation_of_quest_4_agents">The agent is Sentinel.Can hold side alone. The agent have smoke and when you go in them they make a noise.Your question is:</string>
    <string name="question_fourth_agents">Who is this Agent?</string>
    <string name="phoenix">Phoenix</string>
    <string name="killjoy">KillJoy</string>
    <string name="cypher">Cypher</string>

    <string name="fifth_question_agents">Fifth Question</string>
    <string name="explanation_of_quest_5_agents">Raze: \"......, you listen to the weirdest music. Lots of duntz\-duntz\-duntz\-duntz\-duntz. How do you dance to it?\"</string>
    <string name="question_fifth_agents">For which agent raze is saying that?</string>

    //Maps
    <string name="first_question_maps">First Question</string>
    <string name="explanation_of_quest_1_maps">You have the map. Your question is:</string>
    <string name="question_one_maps">Which point is calling Snowman?</string>

    <string name="second_question_maps">Second Question</string>
    <string name="explanation_of_quest_2_maps">You have picture of scheme of some map. Your question is:</string>
    <string name="question_second_maps">Who is this Map?</string>
    <string name="fracture">Fracture</string>
    <string name="icebox">Icebox</string>

    <string name="third_question_maps">Third Question</string>
    <string name="explanation_of_quest_3_maps">You have a picture of the map. Your question is:</string>
    <string name="question_third_maps">Who is this Maps?</string>

    <string name="fourth_question_maps">Fourth Question</string>
    <string name="explanation_of_quest_4_maps">You have a pictures of four maps. Your question is:</string>
    <string name="question_fourth_maps">Which map was first add in the game?</string>

    <string name="fifth_question_maps">Fifth Question</string>
    <string name="explanation_of_quest_5_maps">You have part of drawing: Your question is:</string>
    <string name="question_fifth_maps">From which map is the drawing?</string>

    //Weapons
    <string name="first_question_weapons">First Question</string>
    <string name="explanation_of_quest_1_weapons">You have sound of weapon which is from shotguns. Your question is:</string>
    <string name="question_one_weapons">Which is that weapon?</string>

    <string name="second_question_weapons">Second Question</string>
    <string name="explanation_of_quest_2_weapons">You have picture of weapon. Your question is:</string>
    <string name="question_second_weapons">From which category is the weapon?</string>
    <string name="rifles">RIFLES</string>
    <string name="smgs">SMGS</string>

    <string name="third_question_weapons">Third Question</string>
    <string name="explanation_of_quest_3_weapons">You have a picture of bundle. Your question is:</string>
    <string name="question_third_weapons">What is the name of this Bundle?</string>

    <string name="fourth_question_weapons">Fourth Question</string>
    <string name="explanation_of_quest_4_weapons">You have sound of weapon (You can hear it only one time). Your question is:</string>
    <string name="question_fourth_weapons">What is the Bundle and what is the Weapon?</string>
    <string name="elderFlame_frenzy">ElderFlame - Frenzy</string>
    <string name="elderFlame_vandal">ElderFlame - Vandal</string>
    <string name="sentinel_vandal">Sentinel - Vandal</string>
    <string name="ruination_phantom">Ruination - Phantom</string>

    <string name="fifth_question_weapons">Fifth Question</string>
    <string name="explanation_of_quest_5_weapons">You have picture of agent and weapon which she is holding. Your question is:</string>
    <string name="question_fifth_weapons">What is it the name of the weapon?</string>

    //Toolbar
    <string name="others">Others</string>
    <string name="media">Media</string>
    <string name="leaderboards">LeaderBoards</string>
    <string name="support">Support</string>
    <string name="specs">Specs</string>
    <string name="community_code">Community code</string>
    <string name="social">Social</string>
    <string name="twitter">Twitter</string>
    <string name="youtube">YouTube</string>
    <string name="instagram">Instagram</string>
    <string name="facebook">Facebook</string>
    <string name="discord">Discord</string>
    <string name="game_info">Game Info</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log Out</string>

    //Info
    <string name="we_are_valorant">WE ARE VALORANT</string>
    <string name="defy_the_limits">DEFY THE LIMITS</string>
    <string name="text_info">Blend your style and experience on a global, competitive stage. You have 13 rounds to attack and defend your side using sharp gunplay and tactical abilities. And, with one life per-round, you\'ll need to think faster than your opponent if you want to survive. Take on foes across Competitive and Unranked modes as well as Deathmatch and Spike Rush.</string>
    <string name="learn_the_game">Learn The Game</string>

    //Beginner
    <string name="beginner_s_guide">BEGINNER’S GUIDE</string>
    <string name="txt_beginner1">Straight from the files of Brimstone, this is the VALORANT Beginner’s Guide. Whether this is your first rotation or you\'re needing a refresher, we figure it’s best you take it from the Agent who’s seen it all before.\n \nBelow is what to know before your first game. Pay attention. Might learn something.</string>
    <string name="txt_beginner2">Before you enter your first round, you get to pick from a group of Agents, each with their own role and special skills designed to work alongside each other toward a win. You can dig into the specifics of each Agent on our Agents page.</string>
    <string name="txt_beginner3">After everyone selects their Agent (oh, you picked that one), you’ll jump into a random map and formally enter the first round.\n \nStart a round as either attacker or defender and switch sides in between. Before you do either, you’ll need to navigate the buy phase, which lets you purchase weapons and abilities. What you buy shapes how you can win. Let style or matchups guide your choices.</string>
    <string name="txt_beginner4">No one’s going to tell you how to spend your money, but you’re going to have to pull the trigger at some point.\n \nThere’s a gun for every situation and you can comb the details of each weapon on our dedicated arsenal page. When in doubt, try buying based on a weapon’s type and see how it fits your style, expertise, and your team’s strategy.</string>
    <string name="txt_beginner5">Each map is a different stage to style on your enemies. Flex your creative skills and savvy gunplay for different encounters.\n \nBelow are the basics and you can plot your route using our detailed maps page.</string>
    <string name="txt_beginner6">Yeah, you might already know how to frag an enemy six ways from Sunday, but Brimstone will tell you, most of those ways are pretty noisy.</string>
    <string name="txt_beginner7">No more doubts, you’re ready. But like you, we’re just getting started.\n \nWe’ll keep you updated on the latest Agents, Maps, and more on our news page. You can always keep in touch with us on social for everything else.</string>

    //Game Info Fragment - Agents
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    //Agent Roles
    <string name="duelist">Duelist</string>
    <string name="controller">Controller</string>
    <string name="sentinel">Sentinel</string>
    <string name="initiator">Initiator</string>

    //Agent
    <string name="special_abilities">SPECIAL ABILITIES</string>
    <string name="role_controller">//Role: CONTROLLER</string>
    <string name="role_duelist">//Role: DUELIST</string>
    <string name="role_sentinel">//Role: SENTINEL</string>

    //Brimstone
    <string name="biography_brimstone">// BIOGRAPHY \n \nJoining from the USA, Brimstone\'s orbital arsenal ensures his squad always has the advantage. His ability to deliver utility precisely and from a distance makes him an unmatched boots-on-the-ground commander.</string>
    <string name="brim_ability_q">EQUIP an incendiary grenade launcher. FIRE to launch a grenade that detonates as it comes to a rest on the floor, creating a lingering fire zone that damages players within the zone.</string>
    <string name="brim_ability_e">EQUIP a tactical map. FIRE to set locations where Brimstone’s smoke clouds will land. ALTERNATE FIRE to confirm, launching long-lasting smoke clouds that block vision in the selected area.</string>
    <string name="brim_ability_c">EQUIP a stim beacon. FIRE to toss the stim beacon in front of Brimstone. Upon landing, the stim beacon will create a field that grants players RapidFire.</string>
    <string name="brim_ability_x">EQUIP a tactical map. FIRE to launch a lingering orbital strike laser at the selected location, dealing high damage-over-time to players caught in the selected area.</string>

    //Phoenix
    <string name="biography_phoenix">// BIOGRAPHY \n \nHailing from the U.K., Phoenix\'s star power shines through in his fighting style, igniting the battlefield with flash and flare. Whether he\'s got backup or not, he\'ll rush into a fight on his own terms.</string>
    <string name="phoenix_ability_q">EQUIP a flare orb that takes a curving path and detonates shortly after throwing. FIRE to curve the flare orb to the left, detonating and blinding any player who sees the orb. ALTERNATE FIRE to curve the flare orb to the right.</string>
    <string name="phoenix_ability_e">EQUIP a fireball. FIRE to throw a fireball that explodes after a set amount of time or upon hitting the ground, creating a lingering fire zone that damages enemies.</string>
    <string name="phoenix_ability_c">EQUIP a flame wall. FIRE to create a line of flame that moves forward, creating a wall of fire that blocks vision and damages players passing through it. HOLD FIRE to bend the wall in the direction of your crosshair.</string>
    <string name="phoenix_ability_x">INSTANTLY place a marker at Phoenix’s location. While this ability is active, dying or allowing the timer to expire will end this ability and bring Phoenix back to this location with full health.</string>

    //Sage
    <string name="sage">Sage</string>
    <string name="biography_sage">// BIOGRAPHY \n \nThe stronghold of China, Sage creates safety for herself and her team wherever she goes. Able to revive fallen friends and stave off aggressive pushes, she provides a calm center to a hellish fight.</string>
    <string name="sage_ability_q">EQUIP a slowing orb. FIRE to throw a slowing orb forward that detonates upon landing, creating a lingering field that slows players caught inside of it.</string>
    <string name="sage_ability_e">EQUIP a healing orb. FIRE with your crosshairs over a damaged ally to activate a heal-over-time on them. ALT FIRE while Sage is damaged to activate a self heal-over-time.</string>
    <string name="sage_ability_c">EQUIP a barrier orb. FIRE places a solid wall. ALT FIRE rotates the targeter.</string>
    <string name="sage_ability_x">EQUIP a resurrection ability. FIRE with your crosshairs placed over a dead ally to begin resurrecting them. After a brief channel, the ally will be brought back to life with full health.</string>
    
    //Sova
    <string name="role_initiator">INITIATOR</string>
    <string name="biography_sova">// BIOGRAPHY \n \nBorn from the eternal winter of Russia\'s tundra, Sova tracks, finds, and eliminates enemies with ruthless efficiency and precision. His custom bow and incredible scouting abilities ensure that even if you run, you cannot hide.</string>
    <string name="sova_ability_q">EQUIP a bow with a shock bolt. FIRE to send the explosive forward, detonating upon collision and damaging players nearby. HOLD FIRE to extend the range of the projectile. ALTERNATE FIRE to add up to two bounces to this arrow.</string>
    <string name="sova_ability_e">EQUIP a bow with a recon bolt. FIRE to send the recon bolt forward, activating upon collision and revealing the location of nearby enemies caught in the line of sight of the bolt. HOLD FIRE to extend the range of the projectile. ALTERNATE FIRE to add up to two bounces to this arrow.</string>
    <string name="sova_ability_c">EQUIP an owl drone. FIRE to deploy and take control of movement of the drone. While in control of the drone, FIRE to shoot a marking dart. This dart will reveal the location of any player struck by the dart.</string>
    <string name="sova_ability_x">EQUIP a bow with three long-range wall-piercing energy blasts. FIRE to release an energy blast in a line in front of Sova, dealing damage and revealing the location of enemies caught in the line. This ability can be RE-USED up to two more times while the ability timer is active.</string>

    //Viper
    <string name="viper">Viper</string>
    <string name="biography_viper">// BIOGRAPHY \n \nThe American chemist, Viper deploys an array of poisonous chemical devices to control the battlefield and cripple the enemy\'s vision. If the toxins don\'t kill her prey, her mind games surely will.</string>
    <string name="viper_ability_q">EQUIP a gas emitter. FIRE to throw the emitter that perpetually remains throughout the round. RE-USE the ability to create a toxic gas cloud at the cost of fuel. This ability can be RE-USED more than once and can be picked up to be REDEPLOYED.</string>
    <string name="viper_ability_e">EQUIP a gas emitter launcher. FIRE to deploy a long line of gas emitters. RE-USE the ability to create a tall wall of toxic gas at the cost of fuel. This ability can be RE-USED more than once.</string>
    <string name="viper_ability_c">EQUIP a chemical launcher. FIRE to launch a canister that shatters upon hitting the floor, creating a lingering chemical zone that damages and slows enemies.</string>
    <string name="viper_ability_x">EQUIP a chemical sprayer. FIRE to spray a chemical cloud in all directions around Viper, creating a large cloud that reduces the vision range and maximum health of players inside of it.</string>

</resources>